<resources>
    <string name="app_name">mSanjeevani</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cpractivity">CPRactivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_firstaid">FirstaidActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_first_aid_tips">FirstAidTips</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hospital_list">HospitalListActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_appointments">activity_appointments</string>
    <string name="title_activity_appointments">appointments</string>
    <string name="err_msg_wt">Enter your Weight</string>
    <string name="err_msg_ht">Enter your Height</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_appointment">AddAppointment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_appointment_list">AppointmentList</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sample_activity">sample_activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sample_list">sample_list</string>
    <string name="title_activity_general_instructions">GeneralInstructions</string>
    <string name="generalIns">The First Aid box should be a water resistant, leak proof, air tight and
        drop resistant container
    , with numerous compartments for separating medicines etc.</string>
    <string name="generalIns2">Know what all medications are in box and how to use it.</string>
    <string name="generalIns3">Train others,even kids in your family to use the kit.
    You may be the one who needs first aid.</string>
    <string name="generalIns4">The best place to keep your aid kit is the kitchen. The bathroom has too
    much humidity, which sometimes shortens the shelf life of items.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_aid_box_items">AidBoxItems</string>
    <string name="title_activity_one_click_help">OneClickHelp</string>
    <string name="generalCpr">CPR may be necessary for an adult or children during many different emergencies
    , including accidents, near drowning, suffocation, poisoning, smoke inhalation, electrocution injuries, and suspected
    Sudden Infant Death Syndrome (SIDS).</string>
    <string name="generalCpr2">It should only be performed when a person is not breathing or circulating
        blood adequately.</string>
    <string name="generalCpr3">After CPR , You find an obvious sign of life, e.g.breathing.</string>
    <string name="generalTips">ANIMAL BITES - Apply direct pressure until bleeding stops.
    Gently clean with with soap / antiseptic liquid and warm water. Rinse for several minutes after cleaning.
    Apply antibiotic cream to reduce risk of infection, and cover with a sterile bandage.</string>
    <string name="generalTips1">BROKEN BONE - If the injury and pain is serious then call the ambulance
        or doctor at once. Do not move the broken bone unnecessarily. Place soft padding (clothing, blankets
        etc.). Continue support until help arrives.</string>
    <string name="generalTips3">BURNS - Cool the burn under cool running water for at least 10 minutes.
        The faster and longer a burn is cooled, the less the impact of the injury. If the burn require further
    require care, try to cover it (e.g. with plastic wrap or cover or any ideal covering which does not
    stick to the burn). This will prevent infection by keeping the area clean.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">InfoActivity</string>

</resources>
